ERIC DIMECH

FULL-STACK WFB DEVELOPER

EXPERIENCE

Web Development Teaching Assistant | BrainStation

NOV 2020 - FEB 2021, TORONTO, CANADA

- Provided expert guidance while leading daily stand-ups and open-studio sessions to mentor students and assist with troubleshooting and debugging practices.
- Conducted live coding demonstrations to deepen student understanding and strengthen knowledge of core concepts.
- Accountable for code reviews and providing meaningful feedback when evaluating weekly Sprint submissions with a focus on code quality, visual design and comprehension.

Security & Systems Analyst | Australian Department of Foreign **Affairs & Trade**

SEPT 2017 - FEB 2019, DILI, EAST-TIMOR

- Refocused the Australian Embassy East-Timor risk management portfolio and emergency response protocol policy documents.
- Orchestrated table top emergency response exercises involving the Australian Defence Force and Australian Federal Police.
- Frequently corresponded with the United Nations security stakeholders committee regarding regional and national security concerns.

Community Liaison Officer | Australian Department of Foreign **Affairs & Trade**

MAR 2017 - SEPT 2017, DILI, EAST-TIMOR

- Accountable for direct diplomatic officer support, enhanced sustainable relationships with newly arrived officers through community engagement.
- Achieved the procurement of a complete overhaul on the Australian Missions community recreation center in East-Timor.

PROJECTS

TRAX | Lead Developer



Rollercoaster credit tracking app allows users to create an account and begin logging their coaster riding accomplishments.

Movie Reels | Lead Developer 🗘 🏶





Interactive web app allows users to "nominate" their favourite films.

BrainFlix | Lead Developer



Web app inspired by Youtube.



ericdimech.ca



ericdimech@hotmail.com



416 897 9856



LinkedIn.com/in/eric-dimech



Github.com/e-dimech

SKILLS

React / JavaScript / HTML CSS / SASS Node.js / Express.js Heroku / Netlify / GitHub Agile Development / Figma Firebase Authentication Realtime DB / Cloud Firestore

PROFILE

My story is very unique from a career in marine biology and environmental science to working at a security desk in an overseas Australian embassy. Throughout my life I've always had a passion for technology and built my first website using Angelfire 20 years ago. I want to join a team whose dedication to every challenge continues to inspire my career as a full-stack web developer.

EDUCATION

BrainStation | Diploma Web Development AUG 2020 - OCT 2020, TORONTO, ON

Royal Roads University | BSc

Environmental Science SEPT 2010 - SEPT 2011, VICTORIA, BC

Georgian College | Diploma **Environmental Technologies** SEPT 2007 - SEPT 2010, BARRIE, ON